Senior Software developer and Al Engineer

EHAB TERRA

ehabterra@hotmail.com

+20

106

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ehabterra-271b3a23/ **?**

ehabterra

EXPERIENCE

Freelancing

Senior Developer | since April 2020

Using Golang and Elasticsearch to build insight website. Also, involved in other projects using C#, Angular 8, NodeJS, Typescript and ElectronJS.

Ignite (Remote - Netherlands)

Senior Software Developer | October 2016 - December 2019

Build new features and maintenance websites, services and tools for job vacancies websites in Netherlands and other countries.

Comex

Senior Software Developer | October 2014 - October 2016

Responsible for building a web application for reporting, sales, purchases, warehouses, and real estate.

Hindawi

Senior Software Developer | November 2012 - October 2014

Responsible for Back office website for publishing books and articles.

MENA Software (Remote - Bulgaria)

Senior Software Developer | February 2012 - November 2012

Developing Games Portals, Administrations and Gates websites.

TeBAS, True Technology

Developer | 2004 - 2009

Developed a web and desktop applications for Personnel (HR, Time Attendance, Payroll), Hospital, POS and Restaurant.

EDUCATION

Major in Text Clustering and Data Mining, Cairo University.

Master of Computer Science | October 2014 - November 2020

About me

I have more than 12 years of experience in software development, I involved in the full-stack development of web applications using C#, NodeJs, Golang,...etc for the back-end and AngularJS for the front-end. Beside that, I was publishing researches in the topics of text clustering and feature selection mainly using R as a part of the Master Degree.